// Variable to store questions
let questions = [
    {
        question: "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error?",
        answers: ["Missing of semicolons", "Syntax error", "Division by zero", "Missing of Bracket"],
        correctAnswer: 2
      },
      {
        question: "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that____?",
        answers: ["Both are equal in the value and data type", "Both are not same at all", "Both are x and y are equal in value only", "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well"],
        correctAnswer: 0
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
        answers: ["getElementbyId()", "getElementsByClassName()", "Both A and B", "None of the above",],
        correctAnswer: 0
      },
      {
        question: " Which one of the following operator is used to check weather a specific property exists or not______",
        answers: ["in", "exist", "Exists", "within"],
        correctAnswer: 0
      },
      {
        question: "What if we define a “for” loop and it removes one of the properties that has not yet been enumerated?",
        answers: ["The loop will not run at all", "The removed property will be stored in a cache", "That property will be enumerated", "That specific property will not be enumerated"],
        correctAnswer: 3
      },
      {
        question: "Which one of the following is not a keyword_____",
        answers: ["with","if", "debugger", "use strict"],
        correctAnswer: 3
      },
      {
        question: "Which one of the following is not considered as “statement” in the JavaScript?",
        answers: ["with", "if", "use strict", "debugger"],
        correctAnswer: 2
      },
      {
        question: " In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
        answers: ["block that contains a single statement", "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement", "Conditional block", "both conditional block and a single statement"],
        correctAnswer: 1
      },
      {
        question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression____",
        answers: ["Switch statement", "Alternative to if-else", "If-then-else statement", "immediate if"],
        correctAnswer: 3
      },
      {
        question: "Which one of the following operator returns false if both values are equal?",
        answers: ["==", "!==", "!", "&&"],
        correctAnswer: 0
      },
    // Add more questions here 
]